Sonic-Log Action
Thank you.
Emergency alert!
Unknown ship spotted at 12 o 'clock!
Are they bad guys?
They picked a bad time.
Well, they don't have a
single flag or sail up.
I don't know what kind of ship it is.
It's naked?
Who would do that to their ship?
What are they doing out here without sail?
How should I know?
What's even weirder, the crew is
way too small for a ship that size.
Also, they look like they're
catatonic or something.
They're just sitting around in a daze.
Full speed! Sea monkeys!
Again?
They must have followed us.
Aw, crap, there's no wind!
Hurry and throw us out!
Come on, start rowing!
What's wrong with them?
They're headed towards the sea monkeys.
That wave's going to swallow them whole.
Hey!
Wake up!
There's a giant wave filled
with sea monkeys! Turn around!
Huh?
A ship. Whoa.
It's a pirate ship. Come
on, man. On your feet.
We've got to raid that ship
and swipe their treasure.
Wait, we're going to get
crushed by that giant wave.
Yeah, but we can't let them get away.
Ready the cannons.
You ain't the boss.
Why don't you two?
Turn!
Somebody turn!
Wow, that's got to be the worst crew ever.
Forget about those idiots.
They only want to steal our treasure.
Which way do we turn? Who knows?
Where's the navigator? Give orders!
What navigator? Captain!
What captain?
What the?
Who fired the cannon?
It's too late! We're going down!
You're a bunch of worthless morons!
No, you're a bunch of morons!
What a stupid way!
At least it's calm.
Those gargantuan waves earlier were
actually caused by the sea monkeys.
The humidity and temperature seem
like they're pretty stable now.
So we've got to be in the
next island's climate zone.
You hear that, Robin?
Any islands?
We've been approaching
one for a while now.
Why didn't you tell us?
Look, maybe tell us next
time you see an island.
You know, like this.
Land ahoy! Land!
I see land!
Yeah! Yeah!
Now you say it!
The fog looks pretty thick. Heavy fog?
That's not good.
Hey, chopper, I need you
to stand forward watch.
Right.
Robin, do you have any idea how long
we've been waiting to see another island?
Sorry, won't happen again.
As long as you mean it.
Okay, you know I can't stop
thinking about that ship.
They didn't have a
captain or a navigator or
even sails It was like
they had no idea what
they were doing now What
kind of self-respecting
pirates would head out to see like that?
I'm guessing they got in a battle
and lost captain probably got
killed and then their ship got
plundered But that can't be yet.
I got a look at their ship.
It was in perfect condition
No signs of battle,
but it was still completely
stripped clean of anything a pirate
would need to survive They
probably weren't even pirates then.
Forget it. Mm.
They look like pirates to me,
crummy pirates, but still.
I don't know.
I've got a bad feeling about this somehow.
Have you ever had a good one?
Anyway, I wonder if there's a town.
I hope they got a shipyard.
Reef, don't jump up right away.
I hope we can find a knowledgeable
shipwright to join us.
Get the anchor ready!
We're near the shore!
That feeling just got worse.
Hey, Chopper, Usopp's come down with
another bout of scaredy-cat-itis.
Well, there's no care for that.
All right, let's go, let's go!
There's nothing at all!
Ah!
It's like a blank slate! It's cool!
All I can see is grass and trees!
Man, this place is kind of depressing.
I wonder if anyone
actually lives here. Yahoo!
Hey!
Jeez, it's like they have no
concept of unknown danger.
You can see clear across the island,
and there's no threat in sight.
You see something, Chopper?
Hey!
Human?
Have you ever seen a human
this furry and enormous?
It's got to be some kind of bear!
Whoa!
It's so long!
It's a long bear!
I'm getting dizzy up here!
Hey, check out how long
this apple is! Whoa!
I'm just realizing it, but
the trees are long, too!
Hey, look, is that a house over there?
Yeah, I guess it kind
of looks like a house.
Let's go check it out.
Are you guys related? That's
a deer. I'm a reindeer.
Everything on this island is so long!
How did it get this way?
Maybe it's the gravity?
My body feels so stretched out
just from thinking about it!
What is a point in a place like this?
Hello?
Anyone home?
What do you think you're doing?
You can't go in there.
For all we know, the boss of
the island lives in this house?
And he's probably some
terrifyingly long man-snake?
monster that'll swallow us whole.
It's empty.
No one's home. Huh?
Hey, Luffy, what's up?
There's a giraffe out here.
Really?
Gah!
Chopper, that's not a giraffe.
That's a horse with a long neck.
A long horse.
Yeah, a horse?
Wow, what a pretty horse.
She said thank you, and her name's Shelly.
Going by the saddle she's got on
her, her owner must be close by.
Huh?
Hey, what are you looking at?
Over there.
There's something up with
those two bamboo trees.
Huh?
Yeah, you're right.
Talk about tall.
I can't even see the top.
That's not it. Look closer.
Huh? Uh.
Ah!
They're moving!
They must be part of some wrong animal!
That pig's attacking Loopy!
Are you okay?
Get back here, Bamboo!
Be careful, Loopy!
I'm not!
All right! You did it!
Yeah!
I beat it!
Why are you alone?
Where's your owner?
You don't know where?
That sounds awfully lonely.
It might be bad guys.
Stay there and hide.
What's going on?
Well, uh, I think that bamboo
tree was possessed by this spirit.
Hey, what's the deal?
They blocked in our ship.
This can't be good.
That's the ship I saw earlier.
You looking for a fight?
Because we'll be happy to give you one.
We are the notorious Foxy Pirates!
We want more than just a fight from you.
We want a showdown!
A spirit? Well, yeah.
What else pops out of a tree?
Hey, can you speak?
But acting like I don't
remember you, of course I do.
What have you been up to all these years?
Huh?
You guys know him?
Never seen him. Same here.
Ah, well, that would explain
why I don't remember you then.
Who are you, old man?
And tell us the truth!
If you want my name, it's Tonjit.
But what I intend to
give you is my gratitude.
I've been hoping someone would
knock me down off those stilts.
Off what?
Uh, oh, they are stilts.
We didn't realize because
they were so long.
We couldn't even see you.
I'm not surprised, I couldn't
even see the ground up there.
So then, just to get this straight,
you're not a bamboo tree spirit?
You're just an old guy whose stilts
I happen to think were attacking me!
What were you doing walking
around on those stilts anyway?
Well,
I've always been a stilt enthusiast
So I decided to break some records
and make the world's longest stilts
by using the bamboo on this island.
I managed to get on them
with a little effort,
but then I was too scared to climb down.
That's just plain crazy.
I was up there ten years.
Really crazy?
Wait, you were up on those
stilts for ten whole years?
That's right, and to make matters worse,
the bamboo kept growing the entire time.
It just kept getting harder
and harder to climb down.
So terrifying.
How did you live up there for 10 years?
Well, most of the trees on this island are
just as tall as my stilts, if not taller.
So I was well fed from their fruit.
He talks about it like it's no big deal.
10 long years of his life.
And speaking of stuff that's long,
how come every living creature on
this island is so insanely long?
It might seem crazy to an
outsider, but there is a reason.
As I'm sure you've noticed, the
island is nothing but grass and trees.
It's dull, so everything grew long
out of a longing for excitement.
He can't be serious.
You see that over there?
Platypus.
You just said it longer.
That one is a dachshund dog.
And there are dangerous
animals as well. See?
Over there is a snow leopard.
I'd steer clear of it.
Why is its head the
only thing that's long?
I'm in your debt.
Come to my house and let me
show you some hospitality.
Awesome! I'm starving! Me too!
Acustom in this village
to treat visitors to extra
delicious milk from our
extra-long farm animals.
Village?
I didn't see any village out there.
Or a farmhouse.
All the village is gone!
All our animals, too!
You're nuts, old man.
I know it's been ten years, but
whole villages don't just disappear.
Yes, but this is a special case.
I'll save the explanation until
after we've had a nice cool drink.
I believe I've had some
milk tucked away somewhere.
Did you say milk?
You realize you were stuck on
those stilts for ten years, right?
I hope this cheese is to your liking.
You think we're stupid?
You can't pass off your
disgusting old milk as cheese!
If you don't want to eat
it, I won't force you.
But far be it from me, till
the cheese go to waste.
Wait, so you're saying it's okay
to eat this stuff after all?
Are you out of your mind?
What's the big deal?
Some cheese tastes better
once it's finally aged.
Your high-stress lifestyles
have made your stomachs weak,
whereas laid-back fellows such as
myself can eat whatever we like.
You kids go on your fancy adventures,
but you're shy when it comes to new food.
Someone call the doctor.
What did you think was going to happen?
Mara!
No, no, no!
Someone's going to die!
Yeah, hurry!
Wait, that's me!
It's food poisoning. Yeah, you think?
You're funny, old man.
You okay?
Yes, excluding the fact that the entire
camp packed up and moved on without me.
I see now.
The village didn't disappear, it moved.
That must mean the people here are nomads.
Indeed, and Long Ring Long
Land Island is our home.
You are welcome here.
The island got its name
from its ring-like shape.
Although it's technically one big circle,
the tide's divided into
ten smaller islands.
You probably wouldn't guess that all
of the islands were actually connected,
but once a year,
when the tides are at their lowest,
you can see Long Ring's true
form, if only for a few hours.
We use this time to migrate from one
island to the next every three years,
circling the ring again and again.
Oh, so everyone moved to the next island
while you were stuck up in the trees.
But rotten luck.
That's a good one!
You're a real rebel, old man!
If they stay on each
island for three years,
then subtracting the ten years you spent
living on those stupid bamboo stilts?
it would still take a
good 20 years for them
to come back around and
meet up with you again.
Assuming you don't eat that cheese of
yours and die of food poisoning, of course.
Well, it's sad but true.
I just wish I had my
hoo-ros to ride again.
Then I could cross an island
every time the tides were
low and catch up to the other
villages in only five years.
That's right they're the most graceful and
beautiful animals on
the whole island once.
Tame they can be used to cross the
grassy plains with the greatest of ease.
Without them it would be impossible
for our people to migrate.
After all our belongings
are far too heavy to
carry on our own and even
if we were strong enough
to move all our luggage
the tide would still
rise and drown us before
we could make it across.
Wouldn't it be easier
to take a boat instead?
Yes of course.
But unfortunately we
don't know how to sail.
And besides even if we were
able to charge a log post
here that doesn't mean it
would point to the next island.
The land may be split into ten pieces
but it's all part of the same place.
Suppose I'll just have to wait 20 years.
You'll be lonely.
That's a long time.
Oh wait a second is a horse like a horse?
Hey I almost forgot about that.
We saw a horse on the way here.
Oh my sweet little Shelly you
waited for me all these years.
You're such a pretty girl.
Look at you so cute.
I missed you so much.
You sure grown long since I've been away.
Oh you make me so proud.
Good girl.
That's a good girl.
I'm so sorry if you were.
lonely while I was
gone, it's all my fault.
I promise I'll never leave you again.
What a pow, huh?
Even though everyone else left, she's
still hung around all these years.
That's my kind of horse.
I don't know, it's one of
them is happier right now.
Man, that horse sure is fast, huh?
I want to ride it too.
I see why that old man
likes horses so much.
Now that I'm back,
let's cross the sea together as
soon as the tide is low again, okay?
You've waited through rainy days and
you've waited through snowy days as well.
But from now on, we'll
have nothing but sunshine.
Shelly, are you sure you won't
wait here for Tonjit all alone?
We're taking all your friends with us.
Please come with us, Shelly.
We won't return to this
island for 27 years.
You're going to be lonely if you
have to stay here all by yourself.
We don't know where Tonjit ran off to.
It's not worth waiting here.
He might be gone for good.
Girl, live well.
You know this old man's
afraid of heights, don't you?
Oh, no!
Are you okay?
Shelly!
What happened?
We had a gunshot!
Oh, this cat!
Here, I'll get it!
Sorry, suckers, but that horse is mine!
Yeah, you tell him, boss.
Put those losers in their place.
Whoever you are, you'll pay!
Whoever you are, you don't know?
My goodness, how rude.
Don't tell me you've never
seen this face before!
The only thing I know about your
face is that I'm gonna break it!
He doesn't know me.
Oh, no, don't get depressed, boss.
He's just saying that.
It's a joke.
Everybody knows who you are.
Like you'd have any reason to know him.
You're gonna make him cry, Hamburg!
My name is Foxy.
What's mine is mine, and
what's yours is mine too, Vivi!
You should see the looks
on your dumb faces.
What kind of pants he gets so
worked up over some stupid horse?
If I didn't steal that thing myself,
then somebody else would do it!
That's enough! Come, come!
Hold it, Luffy, not yet!
How'd you know my name was Luffy?
Because unlike some people,
we did our homework. Monkey D.
Luffy with a 100 million berry bounty.
Roro Noah Zoro with a 60 million bounty.
A lump of cash like that
is nothing to scoff at,
especially considering that you
only have seven crew members.
Now, with introductions out of the way,
as captain of the Foxy Pirates, I challenge
you Straw Hats to a Daveyback fight!
I don't know what that means, but
if you want to fight, bring it on!
I'm sick of hearing you talk!
Wait, now it all makes sense.
I bet that messed up
crew we saw on the way
here got challenged to a Daveyback fight,
too!
Which way do we turn? For those!
Where's the Navigator? Give orders!
What Navigator?
Captain! The Captain!
This is bad.
I gotta stop him. Luffy, no!
We're gonna end up losing our crew!
What are you talking about, Usopp?
I know this guy's a jerk, but
you can't agree to fight him!
Hoi, hoi, hoi, hoi, hoi!
Feh, feh, feh, feh!
Oh, too bad, kid.
But don't take backs!
You already agreed, remember?
Bring it on, I believe you said.
Ain't that right Portia.
Oh, that was definitely a bring it on
I heard and once you say bring it on.
There's no turning back That's the rule.
Should have kept your mouth shut.
What's wrong?
Don't tell me you aren't man
enough to keep your word!
You're falling into a trap.
Both of you step aside. Are you crazy?
Shelly waited ten years
for me to come back.
I won't let you take her.
I know that you're angry, but
those are pirates, old man.
You said the fight's already started?
That's right.
A Davyback fight begins
as soon as one captain
accepts the challenge
from the other captain.
No takebacks.
In other words, your captain is fighting
our captain whether you like it or not.
All you can do is sit
back and deal with it.
I don't get this.
If it's a fight, why do
I have to sit and wait?
Let's do this right here, right now.
You don't know anything, do you?
It's not a real fight.
It's more like a sports match
between different pirate crews.
Exactly.
Supposedly, the game originated in a
faraway place called Pirate Island.
As the name implies, it's a sort
of secret paradise for pirates.
At any rate,
the main purpose of a
Davey-backed fight is to
plunder desirable members
from another pirate's crew.
Pirates plundering other pirates? Yes.
No wonder your puny little
crew only has seven members.
A Davy back fight is the best
way to pull in some new recruits.
Since you're so clueless,
I'll tell you how it works.
After each match,
the winner can take any crew member
they want from the losing team.
And once that person is chosen,
they gotta pledge their undying loyalty
to their new captain on the spot.
Both crews take their oath in the name
of Davy Jones, the Pirate of the Deep.
So if you lose, you lose a crew member?
Now you're getting it! Also,
if the losing team doesn't have
any members worth plundering,
the winning captain can add insult to injury
by robbing the ship of its Jolly Roger.
So you're not just betting your crewmates,
but the pride of your ship, too.
Winning might make you stronger, but
losing can leave you with nothing at all.
You might as well be betting your life.
I see.
That explains it.
That ship without a captain
or a navigator or sail.
They must have lost everything
in a Davyback fight.
Oh, so you saw the Fang Frog Pirates,
or what's left of them at least.
How about we give you a chance to
admire our handiwork in person?
Here, let's have a round of
applause for our brand new recruits!
Long live the Foxy Pirates!
Before I came here, I was the
captain of the Fang Frog Pirates.
I was the doctor.
I was the navigator.
And I was the shipwright.
We played five three-coin
games and lost them all.
The captain, 13 crew members,
and our jolly Roger taken away.
With so many people jumping ship, I guess
it was more like a merger than anything.
You're nothing but scum.
We're not playing your stupid game.
Got it?
There's no way we'd
ever sink to your level.
You can say that all you want, but
it ain't the crew's decision to make.
The Davyback fight begins the second one
captain agrees to another
captain's challenge.
What's the matter?
Don't you have faith in your captain?
If you don't agree with
the decisions he makes,
maybe you're better off
joining us after all.
Sorry, Nami, but they're right.
All pirates take an unwritten oath to
follow their captain to the bitter end.
If we turned our back on this fight
now, we'd be sailing away in disgrace.
So? Who cares?
That's better than losing.
Maybe for you, but I'd rather
die than live in disgrace.
The same goes for me. Are you kidding?
Get over yourself!
You know how men can be.
There's no point in arguing with them.
I'll stop Luffy by force if I have to.
Don't bother, it's too late!
All that's left now is to
sit back and wait for the
captains to fire a shot to signal
the beginning of the match.
Oh, no way!
Guess that settles it.
Well, I'm not complaining.
Should be interesting at least.
He's agreed to the game. Yeah!
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
Why didn't you agree?
You could end up losing your crew!
You could lose me!
Oh, I'm gonna win this thing!
Now the Davey Mac fight
is officially underway!
Good!
The sooner I can pound
your face in, the better!
I'd like to see you try!
All right, bring it on, split-head!
He doesn't like my hair cut.
That's not true! Hey!
Apologize to him!
Our boss is sensitive about his looks!
He's sensitive about everything.
He's got a heart of glass.
How many times do I have to tell you?
Don't laugh!
Luffy,
now listen, I'm as angry about the old
guy's horse as you are, but this is madness!
Good!
Use that anger to thrash us!
What are you doing up?
I thought you hurt your back!
Leave it to me!
You don't know what you're getting into.
Sausage on the stick!
Get your sausage on the stick!
We got wrong, we got cheeseburgers,
turkey legs, yaki Sabo, we got it all.
It's time for the opening ceremonies.
You Spear down.
Shut up.
Come on, let's hear the odds.
All competitors, get ready.
Split Head may be a jerk, but
he sure knows how to party.
And check out all the people he invited.
Is that his crew?
Wow, there's so many.
Five jumbo yaki sobas, please.
Whose side are you on, huh?
Now, let's calm down, boys.
We're about to stop.
I love you, Portia! Marry me!
Since our challengers have
never played this game before,
let's go over the rules, okay?
First of all, whatever you
lose in one of the matches,
whether it's your crew, your Jolly Roger,
or anything else,
the only way you can take it back
is with another daily-backed fight.
Second,
any crew member taken
by the winner must swear
undying loyalty to their
new captain on the spot.
No exceptions.
Third, if your Jolly Roger is taken, you
can't ever fly it again. Never ever. Mommy!
I got you some cotton candy!
I don't know how everyone can
be so calm at a time like this.
That's already settled, so you
might as well stop complaining.
Finally,
if you happen to break any of these rules,
you'll be labeled a disgrace to
all pirates and banished to D .B.
Jones' locker.
So do you swear to uphold them?
I swear! I swear!
Then it's settled.
Three coins, three games, orthodox rules.
Let David Jones be our witness.
Huh?
So who's this David Jones guy?
A pirate who was cursed
by the devil and forced
to spend all of eternity
at the bottom of the sea.
I've never heard of
people living underwater.
Well, that's what the legend says.
And all the ships and treasures that
sink beneath the waves go to his locker,
never to be seen by anyone again.
I knew the ocean was
scary, but that's crazy.
Yummy.
Davy Jones has been
taking his picks from all
sorts of pirates for as
long as anyone can remember.
That's why we call it a
Davy-backed fight in honor of
the pirate that may someday
claim your crew is his own.
A captain,
a swordsman, a navigator, a sniper, a
cook, a doctor, and an archaeologist.
So tough, but I do have to decide
who it is I'm going to take.
I believe it to be that one right there.
You jerk.
You've landed us in a real mess, Loopy.
What's the big deal?
All we gotta do is win.
You're forgetting something.
You gotta fill out your team roster.
Our party organizer needs it.
And once you've picked your
lineup, it's set in stone.
We can't lose this thing.
I just know they're gonna
take Captain Usopp if we do.
No, they aren't.
They're gonna take me.
I'm the cute one.
And it's time to announce the rosters.
Each team has chosen to
represent them in today's events.
Because I got a disease that
prevents me from racing.
I don't want to do this stupid
race either, so just man out.
Better not slow me down.
Right back at you.
I'm going to try and hide it.
Oh, who cares? Let's go.
I am Ikaminizu.
You may know me as the Foxy
Pirates party organizer,
but today I will be your commentator.
Our first event of the day
is round one, the Donut Race.
Legal boats for the Donut Race can only be
constructed from two oars
and three empty barrels.
You will be disqualified if
you use any other materials.
This is the perfect chance
for shipwrights to show off.
And time is just about up.
I hope everyone is ready.
It's the Straw Hat team of Navigator Nami,
Sniper Usopp, and Archaeologist Robin.
Their official craft is the Beryl Tiger!
That chick with the orange
hair is smokin' hot.
I am praying that the
dark-haired babe joins our crew.
They can keep the guy.
Yeah, agreed.
Ooh!
Gather round, folks!
The final haunts are end!
Just as I thought!
The top spot goes to our idle
and fellow foxy pirate, Parcha!
Oh, you're too kind!
Joining her is the Fishman Capote!
Their vessel is the cutie wagon
led by the star shark, Mom-Nah.
Yeah, take him down,
Portia, you can do it.
Hold on, you've got a
shark pool in your boat?
I didn't hear him mention any
rules forbidding the use of sharks.
I'll continue to provide
commentary throughout the race?
with a bird's eye view of the
action from atop Chirp Chirp,
a rare South Blue Super Sparrow.
Chirp Chirp!
You're sure this won't sink?
I told you, I am not a
professional shipwright, OK?
Now, on your marks!